reignofblood.net 2011-04-23

# Reign Of Blood - Vampire Game Privacy Policy

banner requires iframes   

## Not yet a member of the free online vampire game Reign Of Blood?

  Contact: To contact us please email reignofblood.net [at] gmail.com

Third Party Adverts:  
ROB will contain adverts around the various pages, many of these being 3rd party adverts. We take no responsibility for what these adverts may contain, but we do try and restrict the type of adverts shown.

Underage:  
If you are under 13 years of age, you must ask permission from your parent/guardian to signup to ROB. If we get contacted informing us that you have not recived permission you will get your account deleted.

Personal Information:  
ROB registration requires you to input your personal information which includes a valid e-mail address and age to authenticate you. Your E-Mail is used to verify your account and to get in touch with you. Your IP address is logged and monitored on this site. This information is only available to staff and used for administration and monitoring purposes.Your information will not be sold or used on any other site but ROB. 

Public:  
This site contains areas where members voice their opinions, where ever this may be. We cannot take responsibility for this, all though we do moderate content on ROB, if you find anything which you find offense contact a member of staff. Also in the public areas there may be links to a external site, we do not moderate any of these external sites so we cannot be blamed for what it may contain. 

Passwords:  
Your password is created and used by you to login to your account. We try to protect our users passwords with care using encryption in db to secure them. But we cannot guarentee their safety, if in the unlikely event of unauthorized access to the db, we cannot be blamed for the loss of accounts/passwords. 

Sharing:  
We will not sell your passwords,emails,personal information to another company. 

**Advertising (Part 2)**  
Online behavioral advertising (â€œOBAâ€) and/or multi-site advertising is occurring.

We collect no data from you via advertisements, the type of data that may be collected are your IP address, geographic location and your browser/operating system details.

As we collect no data ourselves we do not pass anything onto third parties personally. Thirt parties usually use your information to deliver targeted ads to you. [Click here to opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**3rd Party Advertising**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org or click the opt out link above.
